MONICA SAGAR

Address: 3L-8 Shree Balaji Agora Residency, Behind Agora Mall, Ahmedabad Mob: +91 7041811146

Email: monicasagar301@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

To gain more sales & marketing And Back office experience where creative initiative, ideas and a genuine enthusiasm would allow me to progress. To seek quality experience, this allows me to move up in my career graph as well as to learn more things to add in my acquaintance & competence.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Worked as sales executive in Bharat matrimony from April 2016 to May 2017
- Worked as a Back-office and delivery Incharge in Infinium Toyota from Jun 2017 to December 2020
- Worked as Team leader in Bajaj Finance March 2021 to February 2022
- Worked as an Admin in N. K. Anantya (Avishkar Buildcon) from March 2022 to July 2022

EDUCATION

2015

BCA, RAJ BAHADUR MAHAVIDYALAYA, GULALPUR , JAUNPUR

76.58%

2012

EC DIPLOMA, RAJ BAHADUR MAHAVIDYALAYA, GULALPUR, JAUNPUR

73.14%

2008

SSC , NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF OPEN SCHOOLING

50.17 %

SKILLS

- Leadership
- Communication
- Language Known Hindi, English & Gujarati
- Multi-tasking
- Presentation

ACTIVITIES

- Believe in engaging the class with stimulating ideas and thoughts that drive and inspire towards an all-round development of personality and attitude.
- Strongly believe in "Simple living & high thinking".
- Enhancing my skills & knowledge in sales & marketing stream.
- Learn from every disaster & get lesson to come up with the situation.
- Participate in various cultural activities.
- Believe in positivity and happiness in any situation of life is my only motto.

HOBBIES

- MUSIC
- TRAVELLING
- MEDITATION
- COOKING

PERSONAL DETAILS

- NAME :- MONICA SAGAR
- FATHER'S NAME :- PREM SAGAR
- AGE:- 32
- MARITAL STATUS :- UNMARRIED
- GENDER :- FEMALE
- RELIGION :- CHRISTIAN
- NATIONALITY :- INDIA
- ADDRESS:- 3L-8, SHREE BALAJI AGORA RESIDENCY BEHIND AGORA MALL AHMEDABAD